{
  "topics": {
    "Algebra": {
      "topic": "Algebra",
      "prerequisite_ids": [],
      "postrequisite_ids": [
        "Geometry"
      ],
      "subtopics": {
        "Algebra_Subtopic 1": {
          "topic": "Algebra",
          "prerequisite_ids": [],
          "postrequisite_ids": [
            "Geometry_Subtopic 1"
          ],
          "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
          "concepts": {
            "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 1": {
              "topic": "Algebra",
              "prerequisite_ids": [],
              "postrequisite_ids": [
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2"
              ],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
              "concept": "Concept 1",
              "questions": {
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [
                    "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_2"
                  ],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            },
            "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 2": {
              "topic": "Algebra",
              "prerequisite_ids": [],
              "postrequisite_ids": [],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
              "concept": "Concept 2",
              "questions": {
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            }
          }
        },
        "Algebra_Subtopic 2": {
          "topic": "Algebra",
          "prerequisite_ids": [],
          "postrequisite_ids": [
            "Geometry_Subtopic 2"
          ],
          "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
          "concepts": {
            "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 1": {
              "topic": "Algebra",
              "prerequisite_ids": [],
              "postrequisite_ids": [],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
              "concept": "Concept 1",
              "questions": {
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            },
            "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 2": {
              "topic": "Algebra",
              "prerequisite_ids": [],
              "postrequisite_ids": [
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 1"
              ],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
              "concept": "Concept 2",
              "questions": {
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [
                    "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_1"
                  ],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Algebra, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Algebra",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            }
          }
        }
      }
    },
    "Geometry": {
      "topic": "Geometry",
      "prerequisite_ids": [
        "Algebra"
      ],
      "postrequisite_ids": [],
      "subtopics": {
        "Geometry_Subtopic 1": {
          "topic": "Geometry",
          "prerequisite_ids": [
            "Algebra_Subtopic 1"
          ],
          "postrequisite_ids": [
            "Geometry_Subtopic 2"
          ],
          "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
          "concepts": {
            "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 1": {
              "topic": "Geometry",
              "prerequisite_ids": [],
              "postrequisite_ids": [],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
              "concept": "Concept 1",
              "questions": {
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            },
            "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2": {
              "topic": "Geometry",
              "prerequisite_ids": [
                "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 1"
              ],
              "postrequisite_ids": [
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 2"
              ],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
              "concept": "Concept 2",
              "questions": {
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [
                    "Algebra_Subtopic 1_Concept 1_1"
                  ],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [
                    "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_3"
                  ],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 1, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 1",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            }
          }
        },
        "Geometry_Subtopic 2": {
          "topic": "Geometry",
          "prerequisite_ids": [
            "Algebra_Subtopic 2",
            "Geometry_Subtopic 1"
          ],
          "postrequisite_ids": [],
          "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
          "concepts": {
            "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 1": {
              "topic": "Geometry",
              "prerequisite_ids": [
                "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 2"
              ],
              "postrequisite_ids": [],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
              "concept": "Concept 1",
              "questions": {
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [
                    "Algebra_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_2"
                  ],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 1_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 1, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 1",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            },
            "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 2": {
              "topic": "Geometry",
              "prerequisite_ids": [
                "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2"
              ],
              "postrequisite_ids": [],
              "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
              "concept": "Concept 2",
              "questions": {
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_1": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 1",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 1,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_2": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 2",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 2,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                },
                "Geometry_Subtopic 2_Concept 2_3": {
                  "problem": "Problem for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "solution": "Solution for Geometry, Subtopic 2, Concept 2, Question 3",
                  "topic": "Geometry",
                  "prerequisite_ids": [
                    "Geometry_Subtopic 1_Concept 2_2"
                  ],
                  "postrequisite_ids": [],
                  "subtopic": "Subtopic 2",
                  "concept": "Concept 2",
                  "question_number": 3,
                  "difficulty": "easy",
                  "subquestions": [],
                  "code": ""
                }
              }
            }
          }
        }
      }
    }
  }
}